Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up, way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rubbed up to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
Nami's been kidnapped?
It was my fault, they were huge,
but I never saw them coming
They showed up out of nowhere,
attacked, then they left.
First it was centaurs,
now we've got giants too?
What kind of messed up island is this?
An ambush.
So they were tracking us.
That means they're professionals.
They must be. Huh?
I'm confused.
So they didn't come to save Gatorbeard?
Definitely not.
Seems they wanted to kill us
and take the children back.
But then their master, he
made them kill Brownbeard.
They were on the same side.
Brownbeard was so loyal, too.
The Master wouldn't harm children.
He's a one-hearted savior.
We don't know much about this Master guy,
but there are two things I'm sure of.
That he's evil and he's dangerous.
He can't take them.
Who knows what he'll do?
And that's not the only problem.
Nami's still trapped in Frankie's body.
I'm really worried about her, guys.
Yeah, I'll save her somehow.
Wow.
All right, you look after the kids.
Luffy, wait.
Don't forget.
It's my body they took.
Hey, Chopper, I can't
fight in this rat suit.
Give me one of those magic beans
that turns you into a badass.
And make it quick, would you?
What bean?
Wait, the rumble ball?
But that's a drug.
You can't control it.
Not on the first try.
Of course I can.
I'm a super-powered cyborg
with the heart of a champion.
Now hand over the goods, damn it.
We don't have a lot of time to
sit here and argue about it.
Ugh.
Listen, that thing will
make you a monster.
But not for long.
After just three minutes,
you'll be worn out.
Try to do Kong fu point
like I did earlier and...
Way too early!
Come on, Franky, follow me!
Whoa! Stop it!
Why are you trying to squish me?
Whoa! Whoa!
Ricky! I told you! Be careful!
Maybe we should've had him stay here?
He's dangerous right now, but
once the rumble ball wears off,
he'll be too weak to move.
Then he'll be useless.
I don't know where he got it,
but this cyborg Franky fellow
appears to have Vegapunk's laser
weapon attached to his body.
After I cut that garish robot to
pieces and extract the laser system,
his body will be nothing but a
worthless pile of scrap metal.
Prepare the incinerator. Yes, sir.
Those would be ship thieves.
You know, the ones from the Navy.
What of them?
Oh, right.
The battle's raging out of control now.
Oh?
Then we're having trouble.
I mean...
In that case...
Master?
Ah, yes.
This will do nicely.
I'm sure the Navy will make
excellent test subjects.
It's a golden opportunity.
Contact all the centaurs
currently on patrol.
Better make it quick. Right.
Tell our soldiers to evacuate at once.
Unless they want to die, that is!
What do you want from me?
Perverts!
Let me go!
Keep your filthy paws to
yourself, you hear me?
Listen, I understand that
I'm cute and voluptuous,
and you wanted me all to yourselves.
This guy is different.
Hey, whatever he's
into, it's cool with me.
You'll pay for this, jerks!
Just wait until Luffy gets here!
He'll kick your hairy
butts into next week!
Hey, keep your voice down.
Noisy prisoners are...
Not cool.
On the other hand, the laser
weapon built into your body is...
Very cool.
And the reward for bringing
it to our master will be...
Extra cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This wind is so cool.
Almost too cool.
Get some clothes!
To someone your size,
a shot from one of our rifles is
like being hit by a cannonball.
And these are filled with poison gas.
Our targets never see it coming either.
as for your friend of course he'll
come we set a trap to lure him
here he won't be able to resist
following giant footprints in the snow
sweet giant footprints
in the snow how easily
i should follow them this is way too easy
Hey, quit it, Franky!
How many times do I gotta tell you? Huh?
Oh, there's no more footprints!
Luffy and Chopper?
No, wait, that's Franky! Nami!
Be careful!
Their foe's hiding!
Ready, Scotch? Ready.
Pretty Uncle of him not
to notice the cliff.
Are those spikes?
It's all over.
Not a cool way to die.
Armament! Hard name!
Gum-Gum Candy!
Ah, he's a bit trickier than the rest.
Gum-Gum!
Stop right there!
Hooray!
Rayleigh told me it's a waste to
just use this move for defense.
Let's see, what did he say?
Shake the bullets and send them all
right back to him twice as hard!
Now, Kuma Kuma, fire the ground!
Rock!
What did I do to you?
Lay off, Franky!
We've got bigger problems here!
Now I'm burning up.
They might lose their cool,
but I won't lose mine.
Franky!
The cool thing about mountains is
they can be turned into weapons.
Watch out!
The top of that nut's falling on you!
You won't be breaking heads up!
You'll never get away in time!
Look behind you!
He's gonna shoot!
All it takes is one of
these KYP canisters.
And you'll fall into a drunken stupor!
just like the others.
Frank, you did something useful!
Yeah!
Now you're getting it! Good job!
Oh, great!
We're back to this, huh?
Oh, God!
Elephant God!
You went straight to
that trick of the day!
Help!
Uh-oh.
Sorry, Chopper's buddy.
I'll get Chopper to fix you up later.
Wait.
Never mind!
I told you before we have the
home-filled advantage in these mountains.
Just give up. Luffy!
Nami!
Forget it.
I can reach a lot higher than you can.
Whoa, he's not kidding, but...
If I lose him in these mountains,
I'll never track him down again.
It's Law!
Ah, Trafalgar Law, the famous freeloader.
Cool, I'm glad you're here.
Straw Hat Luffy should be right behind me.
Rune.
Ahhhhhhh!
Damn you!
That wasn't cool at all!
All right, counter-shock.
Agh!
Thank you! Ah!
Wait, change me back, creep!
Nami!
Hey!
It's you!
Thanks for saving Nami, buddy!
Look, here's the thing, Straw Hat.
I came here because there's
something I want to discuss with you.
I assume you landed on
Punk Hazard by accident.
But there's an important
key hiding on this island.
One that's powerful enough to throw
the new world into total chaos.
us.
You see, there are only two
ways to live in the new world.
Fighting under the umbrella
of the four emperors or
fighting against them.
And you don't strike me
as the type who likes
to work under someone else.
Yep, that's right, I'm captain. I see.
Well then,
you can work with me huh like how us two
will take down one of the four emperors
I've got a good plan so tell
me so
let me
get this straight
We meet by chance on this crazy island,
and you ask us if we want to
fight an emperor out of the blue?
Look, I don't know what this sleazeball
is after, but I don't trust him.
He's up to no good, Luffy.
I'm not saying killing off
an emperor will be easy.
I just think our odds will be better if we
work together and plan
everything step by step.
What do you say?
This is your big chance.
Well, there's four of them, right?
So which one is it?
Which one is it?
Don't tell me you're thinking about it.
We can't team up with him.
The name of our target.
Right, got it. Huh?
Sure, we're in.
Wado?
Team up with the heart, pirates!
What's the matter with you?
Damn it, Luffy,
how did you manage to go completely insane
in the time you were out saving Nami?
I mean, you weren't
even gone for that long.
Hold on.
This psycho already
scared the crap out of me.
Now we have to trust him with our lives?
Now am I supposed to sleep
at night with him around?
I told you, Luffy.
Let's just forget it. It's risky.
That's why nobody is on board with it.
It's better for us to do
things that are opaque.
She's right.
Besides, it's way too early to think
about challenging the four emperors.
We're just not ready yet!
Hey, Doc.
Fix this raccoon.
Raccoons aren't important right now!
That's me!
Silver!
What did you do to me?
Luffy, I will go along with
this, but we are all pirates.
And where you have pirates, well,
you're sure to have betrayal.
Hey, are you going to betray me? No.
The rest of us are going
to need more than that!
Oh, come on.
A pirate alliance sounds
like a lot of fun, right?
My gut says Traffy's an okay guy.
But even if he's not, what's the big deal?
You guys were training
for the past two years.
I'll let you protect me.
Are you kidding me?
Aw, Luffy.
Look, now I'm flushing.
Thanks a lot, buddy.
I'm super flattered.
I promise we won't let you down.
We're only awesome because it's our job.
There's no need to let her up, you know.
Yeah, don't worry, Luffy.
Whatever happens, we've got your back.
And hey, even if these other wimps
chicken out, you've always got me.
You're gonna be a fool.
Boom.
And shambles.
Dude! Huh?
It's about time!
Man, it's good to be back in my own body!
Almost nobody else I'd rather be than me.
Super!
So you're back. That's great.
But don't ever take possession
of Chopper's body again. Ever.
I'm back.
But I'm not happy.
My body's all busted up now!
Wouldn't have killed you big jerks
to be a little more careful with it!
I'm sorry.
It was all Frankie's fault.
It was my fault?
You're the one who turned into
a monster and flipped out?
All I did was stop you!
With that same overpowered move you used
to beat that kraken, that was overkill!
Fine, you're both jerks!
Yeah, sorry, Chopper.
Well, at least you got
your own bodies back.
Why am I the only person
without my own body?
It's even funnier this way!
My good dummy!
Wow, I'm glad you're
enjoying it! Stop laughing!
But it had to be you!
Chopper and Franky were
both in the same place
when our scary new friends
switched everyone back.
But since Sanji took your body with him
when he went looking for the samurai,
your heart had nowhere else to go.
So if you're gonna be mad at
someone, it should be Sanji!
You can fix it.
Can't you not until your body comes back
So they're all here,
mm—hmm, we gotta help.
Let's
just forget about them too much work;
all of them are addicted to
drugs, yeah, we know that.
I tested them for kids; I want
to take them all back home,
but they need to recover
and build up their strength.
I don't know if we can do anything
about their size—it's sad.
Who would do this to a
bunch of little kids? Well,
the world government for one—for
hundreds of years now they've
been conducting experiments to
try and turn people into giants.
The government, but why would
they do something like that?
If I had to take a guess,
then I'd say it's to
create unlimited giant
soldiers—it's hard to
beat an army like that.
Caesar's probably hoping to figure
out how to do. out how to do
at first, so he can beat Vegapunk
and the government to the punch.
But I don't think
it's that simple.
You sure you want to help them?
I mean, you don't even know
who these kids are, do you?
We don't.
You're right, they may be strangers to me.
But they looked
at me with tears in their
eyes, begging for help.
The Master was able to trick them
into coming to this terrible place.
But once they got here, it
didn't take too long for
them to realize that
something wasn't right.
I'm going to make sure
every single one of them is
safe and sound, and I won't
leave this island until I do.
If I leave with Luffy, are
you going to stay here alone?
Wait, I'm not going anywhere.
If this is important to
Nami and Chopper, then I'll
stay too.
And Sanji wants to put
that samurai back together.
Look, if you're going to work With
us then, get used to helping people.
You have no idea what you're
getting into here, pal.
Here's the thing: see most of the
time when you're forming an alliance,
you have a couple of
groups with a common goal
and you negotiate the
best way to get it done.
Does that sound right, obviously?
So you think, but in Luffy's world that
logic gets thrown out the window completely.
Just means I'm friends
with you frankly—you
could forget about having
any say in what we.
we do.
It's all up to him.
All up to me.
As soon as this guy makes up his
mind about something, that's it.
You're along for the ride
whether you like it or not.
If selfishness was a power,
he'd take out that emperor on the spot.
How do you stand me? Look,
I understand that this is
what your friends want,
but that doesn't concern our planet. Hey!
Stop flicking your boogers at me!
That's nasty!
Just wipe it off.
I can't move right now,
remember? Right, sir.
Fine, but we have to hurry up.
There's no time.
Putting the samurai back together
can be your group's problem.
But I guess I can go investigate the
drug that was given to the children.
Now who's the ship's doctor again?
You come with me.
We'll do research behind Caesar's back.
There, that should do it. I'm sorry.
It's just, I can't walk right now.
I hope you don't mind.
Well, that's a lot of hats, Draghi!
Sorry for laughing, but I just...
Super cute!
Careful out there, Chopper.
You can count on me.
As you could probably all tell
from those assassins he sent,
Caesar wants to eliminate you, as
well as White Hunter and the G5,
so he can take the children back;
he's not gonna stop pursuing you,
not until he gets what he's after.
Before the incident four years
ago when he became a criminal,
he was a government scientist.
Punk hazard is restricted territory;
if word gets out that
someone's been living here,
then Caesar will be forced
to leave his perfect hideout;
that's why he'll stop at nothing to kill.
all of you.
This is a guy with a
bounty of 300 million.
Not only did he eat the Logia-type
Gas-Gas fruit, he's also got
weapons of mass destruction.
Caesar Clown is a force
to be reckoned with.
300 million?
Those of you who can't use
Haki should steer clear of him.
He's extremely tough.
Well, we do have some Haki users.
There's me, Zoro, and Sanji.
Oh, and you.
Yeah, that should be enough.
I'll head over to the lab now.
Be careful out there. Sure.
So we're supposed to kidnap
this master guy, right?
That's the quickest way to do this?
Yeah, that's right.
Wait, what good will it do us to kidnap
Caesar? Money? Oh, no. That's not it.
Caesar's their boss. That's true.
There wouldn't be anybody
to pay his ransom.
What we're after is chaos, not money. Huh?
Chaos?
Sorry, I don't get it.
No point in explaining this now.
We can worry about what lies
ahead when the time comes.
For right now, it's better to
focus on capturing Caesar Clown.
It won't be easy.
As soon as that's done, I'll explain
the whole plan to you in detail.
That said,
once we get our hands on Caesar, that's
going to set everything in motion.
So be ready.
There's no turning back.
Last chance to change your mind.
It's up to you, Straw Hat.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm still with you. Well, all right.
Then I'm more than willing
to cooperate with you.
You just need to make sure
your crew's on board, too.
Uh-huh. Sure thing.
Ah!
Die!
That's Freebar Smoothie,
and Fenbok of the Gourd.
Rope-tugging Chop, too.
I thought so. These people.
As it turns out, they're
all former prisoners.
They just look a little bit different now.
I think you're right.
But what's going on?
The report said everyone was killed
during the incident four years ago.
Smokey!
Why do they all look like that?
I don't know.
Who gives a damn what they look like?
Just keep holding them back, would ya?
We can't send out a signal!
Until we get to sea!
Fire!
Master, do you have a call?
Sir?
Oh, let it ring.
I'm sure it's something
along the lines of we
opened the door and something
terrible was inside.
It's killing our comrades left and right.
Oh, Master, please help us, etc., etc.
Why would I want to listen to that?
I never imagined this island would
be graced with so many visitors.
There's no need to collect
any more test subjects.
Hello! Master! Master!
Please, pick up quick!
We did what you told us!
We opened up that big
door in the Burning Lands!
No good!
The Master won't answer me!
Oh, no!
It's catching up to us!
What the hell?
How far can that crazy thing run?
I don't know, but I don't want
to die like everyone else!
We're done for.
That thing's so huge, we're
never going to get away.
No, please!
Please, don't kill me!
Master, why?
Oh, yes, that's right.
You don't know my pet, do you?
It's a rare specimen.
Its body is made of deadly slime.
Master!
It can be a bit much, but I can't
allow anyone to leave this island.
How does it feel to be
set free after so long?
Smiley!